# GAVIN PIERCE

## BIOSTATISTICS GRADUATE STUDENT

#### CONTACT

206-290-6900

 $\boxtimes$ 

gavinkpierce@gmail.com gkpierce@uw.edu

https://gkpierce.github.io/

0

4558 7th Ave NE Apt 302 Seattle, WA, 98105

#### LANGUAGES

R

Python

Matlab

## **HONORS & AWARDS**

\_\_\_\_\_

UDC Scholar of Hope Recipient: 2021 UDC Dean's List: Fall, 2020; Spring, Fall 2021

# SERVICE

AmeriCorps | City Year | Brooklyn, NY Corps Member | August 2009 - June 2010

# -----

# SKILLS

- Team management
- Project planning and execution
- Trained in bystander intervention and conflict de-escalation
- Effective communication
- · Critical thinking and adaptibility

## ETC.

- Published in Bon Appétit Magazine
- Contracted for international bartending event in Paris, France

#### PROFILE

I'm an aspiring statistician with 7+ years of leadership experience. I have worked with a diverse range of professionals and academics in dynamic environments. Prospectively, I aim to combine a people-facing skill set with my current technical training to become an asset to a rising biotech company.

## EDUCATION

# University of Washington | Seattle, WA

M.Sc. Biostatistics | September 2022 - Present

# University of the District of Columbia | Washington, D.C.

Bachelor of Science | Pure Mathematics | August 2019 - May 2022 GPA: 4.0 / 4 | Summa Cum Laude

### EXPERIENCE

# University of Washington | Seattle, WA

Teaching Assistant Medical Biometry | Fall 2022

Department of Biostatistics Instructor: Lurdes Inoue, Ph.D.

Teaching Assistant Health Sciences Biometry | Winter 2023

Department of Biostatistics *Instructor*: Allison Meisner, Ph.D.

## Room 11 | Washington, D.C.

General Manager | August 2015 - March 2020

Bar Manager | September 2013 - July 2015

- Directly responsible for business operations, team management and marketing
- Oversight of \$1,000,000+ in annual sales
- Led professional development for staff of 20+ employees
- Installed and programmed Breadcrumb POS system

# **Hospitality Consultant | Washington, D.C.**

Bad Saint | 2015-2020

- Developed cocktail program for award winning, nationally-recognized restaurant
- Trained employees on beverage knowledge and best service practices

### Lucy Bar | 2022

- Designed cocktail and wine programs tailored to modern trends and economies
- Instrumental in bar composition and employee training

## La Tejana | 2019

- Specialized beverages for Tex-Mex theme highlighting regional tastes
- Provided logistical structure and essential operational tools

### Sally's Middle Name | 2018

• Trained General Manager in creative development of cocktail program